Guide to the The Nick Zedd Papers 1963 - 2010 MSS.311
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Video recordings, 214741
  - Subseries A: By Nick Zedd, 214762
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation (Dub From Beta)", November 19, 2002; ID: 311.0227; 215894 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0227)
    - "Becchky'd Open Mouth Nite (Unedited Master)", 2002 - 2008; ID: 311.0202; 215891 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0202)
    - [The Adventures of Electra Elf Masters], 2002 - 2008; 215892 (Box 24)
      This is a collection of 45 Electra Elf videocassette masters.
      Media ID: 311.0228 - 311.0229, 311.0233 - 311.0275
    - [The Adventures of Electra Elf Masters], 2002 - 2008; 215901 (Box 25)
      This is a collection of 54 Electra Elf videocassette masters.
      Media ID: 311.0276 - 311.0316, 311.0318 - 311.0319, 311.0321 - 311.0323, 311.0325 - 311.0332
    - [The Adventures of Electra Elf Masters], 2002 - 2008; 215902 (Box 26)
      This is a collection of 8 VHS and 293 Electra Elf Mini DVs.
      Format: VHS, Mini DV
      Media ID: 311.0317, 311.0320, 311.0324, 311.0333 - 311.0337
    - ["The Adventures of Electra Elf" Drafts], 2002 - 2008; 215917 (Box 27)
      This is a collection 89 DVD-R and 2 CD-R Electra Elf moving image recordings.
      Format: DVD-R, CD-R
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: The Complete Series", 2010; ID: 311.0385; 215906 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0385)
    - "Nick Zedd Video: God Dog", 2007; ID: 311.0445; 215919 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0445)
    - "Jake - Designs by Nick Zedd, Monica Casanova", January 16, 2010; ID: 311.0458; 215958 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0458)
    - "Microscope Gallery, Nick Zedd Paintings", 2009 - 2011; ID: 311.0457; 215920 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0457)
    - "Nick Zedd 2011 Microscope Gallery", ID: 311.0446; 215908 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0446)
  - Subseries C: Acting and Press, 215898
    - "Cinema of Transgression Volume 1", c1986; ID: 311.0384; 215910 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0384)
    - "Cinema of Transgression - NTSC (Incomplete)", c1992; ID: 311.0216; 215887 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0216)
    - "Cinema of Transgression - NTSC (Incomplete)", c1992; ID: 311.0215; 215888 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0215)
    - "Cinema of Transgression (PAL Master)", c1992; ID: 311.0214; 215889 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0214)
    - "History of the Avant-Garde: Cinema of Transgression", 1992; ID: 311.0217; 215869 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0217)
      TRT: [02:27:00]
    - "Rage Video Volume II" [copy 1], 1992; ID: 311.0208; 215883 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0208)
    - "Rage Video Volume II" [copy 2], 1992; ID: 311.0209; 215884 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0209)
    - "Nick Zedd on 'Young Gifted and Broke' ", 1993; ID: 311.0232; 215897 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0232)
    - "What About Me" by Rachel Amodeo, November 2, 1993; ID: 311.0212; 215878 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0212)
      TRT: [00:12:00]
    - "Bubblegum Footage with Holly Woodlawn, Nick Zedd Interview", 1995; ID: 311.0218; 215876 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0218)
    - "Bubblegum" by Peter Strickland, 1996; ID: 311.0210; 215880 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0210)
      TRT: [00:15:00]
    - "Joe's Apartment, Previews Starring N. Zedd", 1996; ID: 311.0213; 215890 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0213)
    - "Nick Zedd Poetry Project New Year's Day", 1996; ID: 311.0219; 215877 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0219)
    - "Chicago Underground Film Festival: Nick Zedd Interview, Press Conference", 1996; ID: 311.0221; 215885 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0221)
    - "N. Presley Gershwin Hotel '97: Rebecca, Liz, Andy, Laura, Nick Zedd Projections", 1997; ID: 311.0497; 215996 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0497)
    - "Nick Zedd: Footage of Fellini's Basement, Chicago Underground Film Festival", 2000; ID: 311.0203; 215881 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0203)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview/Open Mike Part 1+2" by Andreas Troeger, 2001; ID: 311.0223; 215863 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0223)
    - "Bulgaria Nightclub NYC: Nick Zedd and Rev Jen Kiss", October 2002; ID: 311.0224; 215862 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0224)
      TRT: [00:06:00]
    - "Interview Nick Zedd, Rev Jen on MNN", 2002; ID: 311.0430; 215922 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0430)
    - "Debate with Rev Jen", 2007; ID: 311.0441; 215923 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0441)
    - "E.E. + Debate Excerpt", 2007; ID: 311.0455; 215924 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0455)
    - "Llik Your Idols", 2007; ID: 311.0383; 215909 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0383)
    - "Nick Zedd Speech, Public Access Hearings", 2007 - 2008; ID: 311.0468 - 311.0469; 215925 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0468 - 311.0469)
    - "Cinema Project Symposium - 4/10", no year; ID: 311.0220; 215875 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0220)
    - "Fabulous Disaster/Strange Love" by Scot-Free, undated; ID: 311.0211; 215879 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0211)
    - "London Film Festival South Bank Part 1", undated; ID: 311.0204; 215854 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0204)
    - "London Film Festival South Bank Part 2", undated; ID: 311.0205; 215853 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0205)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview", undated; ID: 311.0222; 215886 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0222)
    - "Trailer Trash Night of Shame", undated; ID: 311.0207; 215882 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0207)
    - "School of Shame (Incomplete Clone)", undated; ID: 311.0206; 215852 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0206)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous, 214764
    - [Assorted Footage 1], various; 215904 (Box 28)
      This is a collection of 57 VHS assorted recordings from Zedd's personal library.
    - [Assorted Footage 2], various; 215905 (Box 29)
      This is a collection of 55 VHS and 2 Video8 assorted recordings from Zedd's personal library.
    - [Commercial Video 1], various; 215926 (Box 27)
      This is a collection of 11 DVD commercial recordings from Zedd's personal library.
    - [Commercial Video 2], various; 215970 (Box 30)
      This includes a collection of 39 VHS commercial recordings by Zedd's contemporaries.
    - "The Kinks: The Old Grey Whistle Test X-Mas", 1977; ID: 311.0466; 215966 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0466)
    - "Hog Caller Videos, 1 - 7", May 17, 2008; ID: 311.0464; 215964 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0464)
    - "The Feminine City" Short Film and Music by Matt Jones, undated; ID: 311.0465; 215965 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0465)
    - "NYC - Nov. 02" An Essay Shot by Ludovic DuPrez, 2003; ID: 311.0467; 215967 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0467)
    - "Illusion: Travels By Streetcar + Death in the Garden", undated; ID: 311.0470; 215968 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0470)
    - "Jared Whitham X-Mass Special Finnel, undated; ID: 311.0459; 215959 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0459)
    - "The Jared Whitham Show: Escape New York", undated; ID: 311.0460; 215960 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0460)
    - "JWS: 1)Christmas Sandwich, 2)Pizza Future", undated; ID: 311.0461; 215961 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0461)
    - "Marc Slanger", undated; ID: 311.0462; 215962 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0462)
    - "Rare TV Pilots Volume 1", undated; ID: 311.0463; 215963 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0463)
- Series X: Audio, 214742
  Series X: Audio includes original audio elements by and or about Nick Zedd, and is organized chronologically, then alphabetically.
  Subseries A: Film Soundtracks include Zedd production sound effects reels.
  Subseries B: Cassettes preserve Zedd's sound work and interview recordings.
  Subseries C: Miscellaneous includes recordings from Zedd's personal collection.
  Subseries D: Vinyl includes Zedd's work with the Zyklon Beatles and other commercial recordings from his personal collection.
  - Subseries A: Film Soundtracks, 215658
    Access Copies may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - "Police State - B28 G #6, 1st Y2 Police Station", 1987; ID: 311.0017; 215650 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0017)
    - "Police State - City Tone", 1987; ID: 311.0018; 215651 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0018)
    - "Police State - TTE - 1 #2, 2 Minutes Traffic", 1987; ID: 311.0019; 215652 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0019)
    - "Police State - Eerie Tone R3 - 13", 1987; ID: 311.0020; 215653 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0020)
    - "Police State - W.T. Tone Loop", 1987; ID: 311.0021; 215654 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0021)
    - "Police State - City Pres. TTE1 - 2", 1987; ID: 311.0022; 215655 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0022)
    - "Police State - E3-C #9 2x Sirens", 1987; ID: 311.0023; 215656 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0023)
    - "Police State - MS-3 #1 Groan", 1987; ID: 311.0024; 215657 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0024)
    - "Police State - Track Dupe HD", 1987; ID: 311.0025; 215659 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0025)
    - "Police State - Wild Sound HD", 1987; ID: 311.0027; 215661 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0027)
    - "Police State - Sound 43 Filp Extra Transfer", 1987; ID: 311.0029; 215663 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0029)
    - "Police State - Unmarked Reel", 1987; ID: 311.0030; 215664 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0030)
    - "Police State - Scene Two Dailies TRK HD", 1987; ID: 311.0031; 215665 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0031)
    - "Police State" [Unmarked Reel], 1987; ID: 311.0052; 215688 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0052)
    - "Police State" [Unmarked Reel], 1987; ID: 311.0055; 215689 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0055)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Unmarked Reel], 1998; ID: 311.0076; 215704 (Media Shelf, Media ID: 311.0076)
  - Subseries B: Cassettes, 214765
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Master", 1971; ID: 311.0471; 215976 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0471)
      Format: Dynasound Cassette
    - "Attack & Return of the Giant Fly," "Psycolor", 1968 - 1970; ID: 311.0472; 215977 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0472)
      Format: Denon DX1 Cassette
    - "The Perfect Woman" by Nick Zedd with "Dear Nick", c1983; ID: 311.0473; 215978 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0473)
      This element was originally found with "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch" film original.
      Format: TDK D90 Cassette
    - "Lydia Lunch - Copy B", c1983; ID: 311.0474; 215979 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0474)
      Format: Maxell C90 Cassette
    - "Zedd, Kern Interview", February 16, 1986; ID: 311.0475; 215980 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0475)
      Format: Qantem C60 Cassette
    - A) "Nick Zedd Interview," B)"Zedd/Turner Noise Music", 1986; ID: 311.0482; 215987 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0482)
      Format: TDK AD90 Cassette
    - "Nick Zedd Interview, WZBC", December 9, 1988; ID: 311.0476; 215981 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0476)
      Format: Maxell UR60 Cassette
    - "Nick Zedd Interview, KXLU LA", July 24, 1992; ID: 311.0477; 215982 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0477)
      Format: Maxwell UDII 90 Cassette
    - "Kajtek Zedd, Nick Zedd Reads Walt Whitman", 1993; ID: 311.0478; 215983 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0478)
      Format: Memorex dBS Cassette
    - "Guys on Film: Geoffrey O'Brien and Nick Zedd" with "The Poetry Project", January 7, 1994; ID: 311.0479; 215984 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0479)
    - "Zedd Radio Interview, Switzerland", October 9, 1998; ID: 311.0480; 215985 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0480)
      Format: Maxell UDI CD 60 Cassette
    - "Annie Sprinkle: Does Zedd Speak", undated; ID: 311.0481; 215986 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0481)
      Format: Maxell XLII Cassette
    - "Zedd", undated; ID: 311.0483; 215988 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0483)
      Format: TDK IECI/Type I Cassette
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous, 214767
    - [Commercial CDs], c1985 - 2010; 215992 (Box 31)
      This is a collection of 19 CD commercial recordings from Zedd's personal library.
      Format: CD
    - "Kiss Me Now" by Brenda Bergman and the Bodacious Ta-tas, 1995; ID: 311.0484; 215989 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0484)
      Format: Cassette
    - [Nick Zedd, Phoebe Gloeckner, and Shannon Wheeler Interviews], January 8, 2001; ID: 311.0487; 215994 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0487)
    - "Jared Whitham Music (Danger Child at Play)", undated; ID: 311.0503; 215995 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0503)
      Format: CD-R
    - "November Percussion" by Hurst Holt, undated; ID: 311.0504; 215997 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0504)
    - [Untitled Message Cassette], undated; ID: 311.0486; 215991 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0486)
      Format: Microcassette
    - "Worm Movie", undated; ID: 311.0485; 215990 (Box 31, Media ID: 311.0485)
  - Subseries D: Vinyl, 214768
    - [Commercial Vinyl], 1969 - 2000; 215973 (Box 31, Folder 1 - 8)
      This is a collection of 9 commercial vinyl recordings from Zedd's personal library.
      Format: 7" Vinyl
    - "Consume and Die: Generation Z" by Nick Zedd / Zyklon Beatles, 1999; 215971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      Media ID: 311.0505
    - "Karen Black", 1990; 215972 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      This is the musical work of Zedd's contemporary Kembra Pfahler.
      Media ID: 311.0506
    - "Menace Dement", 1990; 215975 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      This is the musical work of Zedd's contemporary Casandra Stark.
      Media ID: 311.0507
- Series XI: Data Storage, 214743
  Series XI: Data Storage includes Zedd's magnetic and optical computer data storage elements organized chronologically, then alphabetically.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - "Nick Zedd in Denmark, #1" by Gritt U.J., May 1999; ID: 311.3.0001; 215481 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0001)
    Format: 3 1/2" Gray Verbatim Disk
    Capacity: [unknown]
  - "Nick Zedd in Denmark, #2" by Gritt U.J., May 1999; ID: 311.3.0002; 215482 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0002)
  - "Zedd Cast on Set, Marguerite", July 12, 2003; ID: 311.3.0003; 215483 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0003)
    Format: 3 1/2" Green IBM Imation 2HD Disk
    Capacity: 1.44 MB
  - "Zedd: 3 Maggot Stills", 2003; ID: 311.3.0004; 215486 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0004)
    Format: 3 1/2" Green IBM Imation 2 HD Disk
  - "Zedd Maggot 2003", ID: 311.3.0005; 215487 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0005)
    Format: 3 1/2" Blue IBM Imation 2HD Disk
  - [Kodak Picture Disk, 1 of 2], December 3, 2000; ID: 311.3.0006; 215488 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0006)
    Format: 3 1/2" Red Kodak Disk
    Capacity: 8 MB
  - [Kodak Picture Disk, 2 of 2], December 3, 2000; ID: 311.3.0007; 215489 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0007)
  - "Zedd on Set", July 2003; ID: 311.3.0008; 215490 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0008)
  - [P.O. SHOUT Magazine], undated; ID: 311.3.0009; 215491 (Box 12, Media ID: 311.3.0009)
    Format: 3 1/2" Gray Iomega Disk
  - [Photography and Software], undated; 215993 (Box 31)
    This is a collection of 12 CD-R assorted recordings from Zedd's personal files.
    Media ID: 311.0488 - 311.0494, 311.0498 - 311.0502
- Series XII. Accretions, 277346
  - 2016 Accretion: AUUUUU Zine and La Jornada Newspaper, 2016, undated; 277347 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Writing, 215464
  - Subseries A: Zedd A - Z, 215465
    - Wallpaper Zine [Fragments, 1 of 2], c1983 - 1990; 215493 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Wallpaper Zine [Fragments, 2 of 2], c1983 - 1990; 215618 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Synopsis, Blue Scrapbook Cover], c1992; 215494 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Juvenelia, 215467
    - The Beacon Volume 9, Number 4 [High Point High School of Beltsville, MD], January 1963; 215614 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The Beacon Volume 19, Number 4, December 14, 1973; 215615 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "Essay" by James Harding for Prattler Volume 39, Number 5, December 20, 1976; 215496 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Prattler Volume 41, Number 4, November 20, 1978; 215616 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Venusian Press [Sketches removed from XINE Sketchbook], 1969 - 1971; 215495 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Subseries C: Source and Subject Files, 215497
    - CMLL De Lucha Libre Official Calendar, 2010; 215617 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - [Comic Sketches of Nick Zedd and Taylor Mead], undated; 215498 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - [Lydia Lunch Posters], undated; 215524 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - [Johnny Rotten Poster], undated; 215525 (Folder 1 Right)
    - [Willy Deville Poster], undated; 215526 (Folder 2 Right)
  - Subseries D: Other Authors, 215499
    - "In Praise of Hardcore" by Kenneth Tynan, undated; 215500 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - "Dream" by Casandra Stark for Underground Film Bulletin, June 28, 1985; 215527 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Projects, 215501
  - Subseries A: Development, 215502
    - "Destination X" [Sketches removed from "Johnny Satan" Sketchbook], c1977; 215503 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - "Destination X" [Animation Cells], 1976; 215504 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "Johnny Satan" [Sketches removed Black Sketchbook], c1976; 215505 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Distribution, 215506
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Posters], undated; 215507 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Mock-Up Poster Prints for Incomplete Feature with Notes], c2009; 215508 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - "The Bogus Man" [Poster for East Village Eye], June 30, 1980; 215528 (Folder 7 Right)
    - [Flyers of Events Featuring Zedd 1], various; 215509 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - [Flyers of Events Featuring Zedd 2], various; 216641 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo" [Flyers], 1983; 215510 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo" [Poster Illustration by T. Smith], 1982; 216150 (Folder 6 Right)
    - "Lord of the Cockrings" [Posters], 2001; 216643 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - "Me Minus You" [Flyers], 1985; 216644 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - [Nick Zedd at Beursschouwburg Program, Belgium], April 11 - 31, 1997; 215619 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - [Nick Zedd: Cinema of Transgression at Werkstattkino Malseh'n Program, Germany], March 1990; 215620 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - "No Such Thing As Gravity" [Posters], 1990; 216645 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Penetration Films [Case Graphics, Mock-Ups], undated; 215511 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - "Police State" [Flyers], c1987; 216646 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - "Police State" [Poster Illustration], c1987; 216151 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - [Poster Advertisements for Events Featuring Zedd], various; 215529 (Folder 5 Right)
    - "The Raunchy World of Nick Zedd: Sleaze Cinema" [Poster], c1988; 216652 (Folder 4)
    - "Shadows in the City" [Posters], c1990; 215530 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - "Thrust in Me" [Mounted Self Portraits], 1998; 216647 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Poster Mock-Ups], 1992; 215512 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Mounted Stills 1], c1992; 216630 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Mounted Stills 2], c1992; 216631 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Mounted Stills 3], c1992; 216632 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Mounted Stills 4], c1992; 216648 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Poster with Mounted Stills], 1998; 216634 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo/The Adventures of Electra Elf: Vile Buddies" [Poster], c2006; 216653 (Folder 28)
    - "Nick Zedd Undergroundfilme aus New York" at Die Rohre Program [Germany], March 1990; 215611 (Folder 26)
  - Subseries E: Other Artists and Events, 215513
    - [Flyers of Events Not Featuring Zedd], various; 215514 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Giorno Poetry Systems AIDS Treatment Project Poster, undated; 215531 (Folder 4 Right)
    - MOMA PS1 Newspaper, Spring 2009; 215532 (Folder 3 Right)
    - [Posters of Events Not Featuring Zedd], 1988, 1996; 215612 (Folder 27)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Dad's Pornography Collection, 215515
  - [Assorted Posters], c1942, 1960s; 215516 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Photography, 215517
  - Subseries A: Professional, 215518
    - [Donna Death Portraits], 1979 - 1983; 215519 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - [Monica Casanova Portraits], undated; 216635 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - [Press Photographs of Zedd], undated; 215520 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Personal, 216636
    - [Mounted Halloween Photograph], November 24, 1975; 216637 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- OVERSIZE Series VI: Illustrations and Artwork, 215521
  - [Halloween Party Scene Illustration], undated; 215522 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - [Illustrations of Nick Zedd], undated; 216649 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - [Lucha Libre Sketch], undated; 216650 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - "Prevent Senseless Tragedy / Bizarreness of Fantasies of Grandville" [Painting], undated; 215523 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- OVERSIZE Series VII: Objects, 215534
  - Subseries A: Props, 216152
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" ASS Magazine Styroboard Sign, 2002 - 2008; 216153 (Folder 1 Right)
  - Subseries B: Zedd - Casanova Clothing, 215535
    - [Green Pleated Mini Skirt with "Electra Elf" Screen Print], undated; 215555 (Box 17, Object ID: 311.2.0013)
    - [White Sleeveless T-Shirt with "Electra Elf" Screen Print], undated; 215554 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0014)
    - [Yellow Sweatshirt with "Electra Elf" Screen Print], undated; 215553 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0015)
    - [Blue T-Shirt with "Electra Elf" Screen Print], undated; 215552 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0016)
    - [Two Tan T-Shirts with "Electra Elf" Screen Print], undated; 215551 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0017)
    - [Yellow Thermal Shirt with "Electra Elf" Screen Print], undated; 215550 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0018)
    - [Red T-Shirt with "Cinema of Transgression, Volume 1" Patch], undated; 215549 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0019)
    - [Black T-Shirt with "Cinema of Transgression, Volume 1" Patch], undated; 215548 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0020)
    - [Pink Sweatshirt with "Whoregasm" Screen Print], undated; 215547 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0021)
    - [Black T-Shirt with "Geek Maggot Bingo" Patch], undated; 215546 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0022)
    - [Black Sweatshirt with "They Eat Scum" Patch], undated; 215545 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0023)
    - [White Blouse with Zedd Filmography Prints], undated; 215544 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0024)
    - [Yellow Blouse with Zedd Filmography Prints], undated; 215543 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0025)
    - [Yellow Blouse with Zedd Filmography Prints], undated; 215542 (Box 36, Object ID: 311.2.0026)
    - [Gray Pleated Skirt with Screen Print of Richard Hell], undated; 215541 (Box 17, Object ID: 311.2.0027)
    - [Black Pleated Mini Skirt with "Geek Maggot Bingo" Screen Print], undated; 215540 (Box 17, Object ID: 311.2.0028)
    - [Houndstooth Pleated Skirt with "Geek Maggot Bingo" Screen Print], undated; 215539 (Box 17, Object ID: 311.2.0029)
    - [Maroon Pleated Mini Skirt with Screen Print of Richard Hell], undated; 215538 (Box 17, Object ID: 311.2.0030)
    - [Green Pleated Skirt with Screen Print of Richard Hell], undated; 215537 (Box 17, Object ID: 311.2.0031)
    - ["Geek Maggot Bingo" Brenda Bergman and Richard Hell Screenprint Stencil], undated; 216148 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - ["Geek Maggot Bingo" Donna Death Screenprint Stencil], undated; 216149 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ["Geek Maggot Bingo" Richard Hell Screenprint Stencil], undated; 216146 (Box 37, Object ID: 311.2.0035, Folder 1)
    - ["The Adventures of Electra Elf" Screenprint Stencil], undated; 216147 (Box 38, Object ID: 311.2.0035)
    - [Zedd - Casanova Clothing Transparencies], undated; 216651 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: The Mexican Kit, 215557 (Box 18, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 47, Box 45, Box 46, Folder 10, Folder 13 Left)
    - [Tapestry textile], undated (Folder 10, Object 311.2.0037)
    - [Paper cutouts], undated (Folder 13 Left, Object 311.2.0038)
    - [Chalice with red cloth], undated (Box 46, Object 311.2.0039)
    - [Decorative object with streamers], undated (Box 46, Object 311.2.0040)
    - [Metal candle stick], undated (Box 47, Object 311.2.0041)
    - [Glass pyramid], undated (Box 47, Object 311.2.0042)
    - [Skeleton virgin mary with glitter], undated (Box 47, Object 311.2.0043)
    - [Skeleton with glitter], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0044)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0045)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0046)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0047)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0048)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0049)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0050)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0051)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0052)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0053)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0054)